Register of the Hugh Gibson papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1902-1954 (Boxes 10-67)
  - Craigie, R. Leslie, 1930-1931
  - Cravath, Paul, 1920
  - Creel, George, 1918 (Box 20)
  - Crews(?), Margaret, 1922
  - Crocker, Edward S., 1924
  - Crocker, Gertrude E., 1919
  - Crocker, Henry J., 1930
  - Crocker, Stuart M., 1933
  - Cronan, W. P., Mrs., 1930
  - Crosby, Chuffy, 1920-1936
  - Crosby, Sheldon Leavitt, 1925-1930
  - Crossett, John B., 1927
  - Crowder, E. H., 1913-1929
  - Cruger, Alexander Pendleton, 1919-1928
  - Cuban delegation to the League of Nations, undated
  - Cudahy, John, 1934-1943
  - Cumming, Hugh, 1953
  - Cumming, Hugh S., Jr., 1934-1953
  - Cummings, Miss, 1936
  - Curti, Arthur, 1927
  - Curtis, Edward Davison, 1915-1922
  - Curtis, Emerson, 1928
  - Curtis Brown Ltd., London, 1927-1930
  - Czapski, Emeric, Count, 1921-1952
  - Czarnowska, Eleanora, 1921-1922
  - Czartoryski, Olgierd, 1924
  - Darney(?), Kattarine, 1922
  - Daubeny, C. J., 1930
  - Davie, May (Mrs. Preston), 1952-1954
  - Davies, David, 1932
  - Davila, Miguel R., 1909
  - Davis, Ben G., 1923
  - Davis, D. A. (The Progressive College; The International W.M.C.A. School, Geneva), 1933
  - Davis, Harry Edgar, 1932
  - Davis, Hugh, 1954
  - Davis, Livingston, 1920-1929
  - Davis, Malcom W., 1926
  - Davis, Mary, 1954
  - Davis, Norman H., 1920-1938
  - Davis, Richard Harding, undated
  - Davis, Robert Beale, 1920
  - Dawes, Charles G., Gen., 1929-1941
  - Dawes, Henry, 1932
  - Dawson, Allan, 1935-1936
  - Dawson, Geoffrey, 1941
  - Dawson, Warrington, 1919-1933
  - Dawson, William, 1921-1934
  - Day, Arden L., 1930-1936
  - Dean, Basil, 1930
  - Dearing, Fred Morris, 1919-1936
  - Deboever, Alice, undated (Box 21)
  - De Courcy, Kenneth, 1953
  - Deering, John A., 1932
  - Deisler, Paul F., 1928-1929
  - Delacroix, Leon, 1927
  - Delme-Radcliffe, Charles, 1926
  - De Masi, H. Armand, 1933
  - Den, Ray, 1954
  - Dennis, William Cullen, 1919-1933
  - Derby, Ethel, 1928
  - Desvernine, Raoul, 1952
  - De Ville, John Baptist, Father [See also: Sartori di Montecroce, Anna, Baroness], 1932
  - Dexter, Fletcher, 1924-1929
  - Dewey, C. S., 1930
  - Dewey, Thomas E., 1943
  - De Witt, J. L., Col., 1927
  - Dinichert, Paul, 1925
  - Ditmars, Walter E., 1953-1954
  - Dixon, Gertrude C., 1926
  - Dmowski, Roman, 1919
  - Dobrowski, M. H., 1920-1921
  - Dod, Clara E., 1927
  - Dodd, Mead and Co., N.Y., 1934
  - Dodd, William E., 1935
  - Dodge, H. Percival H. [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson], 1921-1926
  - Doerman, A., 1919
  - Dolbeare, Frederick R. [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson]
    - 1918-1924
    - 1925-1954
  - Donaubaur, 1931
  - Donnally, Harry H., 1926
  - Donovan, William L., Col., 1920-1941
  - Doran, J., 1928
  - Dosch-Fleurot, Arno, 1923-1936
  - Doss, Corwin M., 1924-1930
  - Doss, Milburn, 1921
  - Doty, Madeleine Z., 1926
  - Doty, S. W., 1926-1927
  - Doubleday & Company Inc., N.Y. [See: Robins, Robbie]
  - Doubleday, Russell (Doubleday, Page & Co.), 1918-1927
  - Doughty, H. R., 1923
  - Downey, Fairfax, 1932
  - Doyle, W. T. S., 1928-1936
  - Drake, E. Millington, 1925
  - Drake, Sarita, 1953
  - Dravo, Hudson D., 1933-1936
  - Dresel, Ellis Loring, 1919-1924
  - Drugman, 1922
  - Drummond, Eric, Sir, 1924-1933
  - Duarte, Luis M., 1926
  - Duffek, Adolphe, 1928
  - Duggan, A. L., 1927
  - Duggan, Laurence, 1936
  - Duggan, Mary Alice, 1926
  - Duggan, Stephen P., 1923
  - Dulles, Allen Welsh (Box 22)
    - 1918-1925
    - 1926-1927
    - 1928-1954
  - Dulles, John Foster, 1953
  - Dunham, George B. and Jessie, 1919-1936
  - Dunn, Gano, 1925
  - Dunn, James Clement, 1923-1954
  - Dunn, Julia, undated
  - Dunning, J. J., 1930
  - Dupont, Gen., 1923
  - Durand, E. Dana, 1920-1925
  - Durand, William Dana, 1931
  - Duras, Victor Hugo, 1932
  - Durazzo, Marquise, 1930
  - Durham, John Selwyn, 1928
  - E.D.I.C., Paris, 1952
  - Eadie, James, 1929-1933
  - Earle, Homer P., 1921-1936
  - Eberhardt, Charles C., 1923
  - Ecole Libre des Sciences Politiques, Paris, 1924
  - Eden, Anthony, 1943-1953
  - Edgar, William C., 1920
  - Edge, Walter E. [See also: DISARMAMENT CONFERENCES, General Disarmament Conference, Correspondence with Walter E. Edge], 1931
  - Edmunds, C. K., 1934
  - Edwards, L. A., 1926
  - Egan, Martin, 1918-1926
  - Ehman, Mr., 1953
  - Ehrlich, Carl, 1926-1933
  - Einstein, Lewis, 1922-1936
  - Elio, Tomas M., 1935 (Box 23)
  - Elisabeth, Queen of Belgium, 1934-1936
  - Elizalde, Rafael, 1928
  - Elst, Jo, Baron, and Baroness Allie van der, 1950-1954
  - Eltz, Eleanore von, 1926
  - Elwes, Simon, 1952-1953
  - Elwes, Monseignor, 1941
  - Ely, Gertrude, 1926
  - Ely, James B., 1930
  - Emerson, Haven, 1927
  - Erhardt, John G., 1934
  - Erice, 1953
  - Erice, Jose de, 1930
  - Erk, Edmund Frederick, Col., 1926-1929
  - Eshman, Jo, 1932
  - Esley, Bertram T., 1936
  - Etelka, undated
  - Ewing, Helen Hadley (Mrs. J. L.), 1932
  - Faille, J. Della, Baroness, 1926
  - Farman, Elbert E., Col., 1921-1927
  - Farnham, Charles W., 1920-1931
  - Farquhar, Harold, 1924-1928
  - Fatio, Louis J., 1926
  - Faunt-Leroy, Cedric, Col., 1920-1932
  - Federation Universitaire Internationale pour la Societe des Nations, Paris, 1926
  - Felber, 1927
  - Felix, Prince of Luxemburg, 1937
  - Ferguson, Charles, 1920
  - Ferguson, Donald, 1933
  - Ferrero, Constantin, 1952
  - Field, Frederick V., 1925
  - Filipowicz, Tytus, 1931
  - Finley, David, 1931
  - Finley, John H., 1921
  - Finley, Martha Boyden, 1923
  - First Methodist Episcopal Church (Walter H. Smith), 1928
  - Fitz Alan of Derwent, Viscount, 1925-1930
  - Fitz Patrick, F., 1928
  - Fitzgerald, F. E., 1953
  - Flanders, Count of, 1934
  - Fleming, Frank, 1919
  - Fletcher, Alfred C. B., undated
  - Fletcher, Henry P. [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson], 1921-1934
  - Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy, Medford, Mass., 1952
  - Flint, Francis P., 1907
  - Flournoy, Richard, undated
  - Foa, Carlo, 1934
  - Fogbaum, R. F., Jr., 1922
  - Foley, William T., 1952-1954
  - Font, Mariano, 1924
  - Fontaine, Jean de, 1928
  - Fontes, Ernesto, undated
  - Ford, J. D. M., 1930
  - Forestier, J. C. N., 1928
  - Forster, Arnold, 1932
  - Forthomme, Pierre, 1930
  - Fortune, N.Y., 1934
  - Foster, Carol H., 1934-1936
  - Foster, George H., 1928
  - Foster, Reginald, 1920-1921
  - Foster, Reginald C., 1919-1924
  - Fotitch, Constantin, 1933
  - Fowle, Charles W., 1920
  - Fowler, Emily G. (Mrs. William Eric), undated
  - Fowler, Harold, Col., 1921-1932
  - Foy, R. C., Col., 1931
  - Franck, Louis, 1928
  - Francois, Leon, Mrs., 1928
  - Francqui, Emile, 1927-1933
  - Frank, Glenn (The Century Company, N.Y.), 1922
  - Franks, Grace A. G., 1925-1954
  - Fraser, Maj., undated
  - Frazer, Robert, Jr., 1925
  - Frazier, Arthur Hugh, 1920-1925
  - Frear, James A., 1929
  - Freeman, Henrietta B., 1936
  - Freitas Valle, Ciro, 1934
  - Fremont, Jessie and John, 1931-1932
  - Frick, Donald J., 1924-1953 (Box 24)
  - Frick, Margaret, 1925-1934
  - Fritsch, John F., Jr., 1928
  - Fronczak, Francis E., 1924
  - Frost, C. L., 1935
  - Frost, Holloway H., Commander, 1927-1930
  - Frost, Wesley, 1935
  - Frothingham, Donald, 1920-1922
  - Fruhwirth(?), Cardinal, 1925
  - Fuller, Mrs., 1936
  - Fuller, W. Parmer, Jr. and Adeline, 1921-1927
  - Fyfe, Howard, 1932
  - Gagnon, Clarence A., 1926-1935
  - Gagnon, Kathryn I., 1910
  - Galen, Sophie, Countess, 1953-1954
  - Gallatin, Emile Morris, undated
  - Gallet, undated
  - Galpin, Perrin C. [See also: SUBJECT FILE, C.R.B. Educational Foundation, Inc.], 1920-1954
  - Gampert, Emile, 1932
  - Gardner, Lester D., 1928-1930
  - Garner, Wilford J., 1929
  - Garrett, John W. [See also: DISARMAMENT CONFERENCES, General Disarmament Conference, Correspondence with John W. Garrett], 1919-1936
  - Garrette, Eve, 1943
  - Garvin, J. L., 1930-1931
  - Gary, Hampson, 1920
  - Gase, W. E., 1953
  - Gaskill, Charles S., Col., 1921
  - Gaspari, Cardinal, 1922
  - Gassera, 1925
  - Gay, Edwin F., 1920
  - Gay, George Innes, 1921
  - General Motors Corporation, N.Y., 1953
  - General Motors Export Company, N.Y., 1924
  - Gerry, Harvey L., 1929-1930
  - Gerson, Louis J., 1929
  - Geynst, J. de, 1927
  - Gherardi, Walter, 1929-1930
  - Gibbons, Helen Davenport, 1921
  - Gibbons, Herbert Adams, 1920
  - Gibson, Carleton B., 1921
  - Gibson, David H., 1931
  - Gibson, Hugh, 1930
  - Gibson, J. M., 1922
  - Gibson, Mary
    - 1909 April-May (Box 25)
    - 1909 June - 1910 July (Box 26)
    - 1910 August - 1911 August (Box 27)
    - 1911 September - 1912 August (Box 28)
    - 1912 September - 1913 October (Box 29)
    - 1913 November - 1914 May (Box 30)
    - 1914 June-August (Box 31)
    - 1914 September - 1915 February (Box 32)
    - 1915 March - 1916 July (Box 33)
    - 1916 August - 1917 September (Box 34)
    - 1917 October - 1919 April (Box 35)
    - 1919 May - 1920 April (Box 36)
    - 1920 May - 1921 May (Box 37)
    - 1921 June - 1922 July (Box 38)
    - 1922 August - 1923 September (Box 39)
    - 1923 October-1928 (Box 40)
    - 1929, 2.0 folders (Box 41)
    - 1930
  - Gibson, Michael, 1952-1954
  - Gibson, Peter, 1953
  - Gibson, Precentor William, Rev., 1929-1933
  - Gibson, Ynes
    - Letters
      - 1934
      - 1935
      - 1938-1946
    - Telegrams, 1922-1937
  - Gilbert, Manson, 1930 (Box 42)
  - Gilbert, Prentiss B., 1928-1933
  - Gilbert, S. Parker, 1928
  - Gilchrist, Huntington, 1924-1928
  - Gill, Capt., undated
  - Gilson, Henry, 1932
  - Gipson, James H., 1952
  - Giusti del Giardino, Justo, Count, 1953
  - Gizyka, Eleanor, Countess, 1921-1922
  - Glazebrook, Otis A., 1924
  - Glenn, Otis F., 1932
  - Glennon, John, 1934
  - Glinka, Ladislas, 1920
  - Godoy, Albert L., 1929
  - Godson, F. A., Col., 1924
  - Goedecke, Walter J., 1920-1924
  - Goetz, Robert C. F., 1931-1952
  - Goetz, William, 1933-1934
  - Gonzales, William E., 1923
  - Gonzalez, Antonio C., 1935
  - Goode, R. N., 1920
  - Goode, William, 1931
  - Goodheart, Arthur L., 1930
  - Goodheart, A. C., Col., 1920-1925
  - Gordon, George A., 1927-1936
  - Gordon, P. Paul, Father, 1953
  - Gorlof, 1924
  - Gowen, Franklin C., 1947-1954
  - Grandi, Dino, 1930
  - Grant, Nesta, 1953
  - Grant-Smith, Ulysses [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson], 1919-1924
  - Graves, J. A., 1927
  - Gray, Prentiss N., 1920-1933
  - Greely, John Nesmith, 1929
  - Green, Joseph C., 1918-1936
  - Green, Betty (Mrs. Gordon), 1954
  - Green, Ida A., 1926
  - Greene, Caroline S. (aunt of Gibson), 1921-1936
  - Greene, Eva Hirdler (Mrs. F. C.), 1927
  - Greene, George S., 1927
  - Greene, Winthrop S., 1933
  - Greenough, William, 1924
  - Gregory, T. T. C., 1919-1927
  - Grenier, Baroness, 1953
  - Grew, Joseph C. [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson]
    - 1910-1923
    - 1924-1925
    - 1926-1936 (Box 43)
  - Grimes, Lyman, 1925
  - Groati, Carl D., 1951
  - Grocholsky, Remi, 1934
  - Grodski, Stanislaw, 1921-1923
  - Groedel, Franz M. [See: Kerckhoff, Louise E.]
  - Grollemund, J., Lt. Col., 1925
  - Grosjean, Paul, 1952-1954
  - Grosser, Freda, 1921
  - Grove, William R., 1920
  - Groves, J. Philip [See also: DIPLOMATIC POSTS, Belgium, Correspondence with Embassy, Groves, J. Philip], 1927-1952
  - Groves, Leslie R., 1953
  - Grunne, Charles de Hemricourt de, Count, 1933
  - Grunne, Guillaume de Hemricourt de, Count, 1925-1954
  - Grunne, Eugene de, Count, 1928
  - Guggenheim, Harry F., 1927
  - Guggenheimer, Untermeyer & Marshall, N.Y., 1920
  - Guillaume, Elizabeth (Baroness Jules), born Wittouck, 1923-1933
  - Guinle, Carlos, Mrs., undated
  - Gunther, Franklin M. [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson], 1919-1934
  - Gurney, F. W., 1929
  - Gurney, H., Sir, undated
  - Gustavo Guerrero, J., 1929
  - Gutt, Camille, 1932
  - Gwynn, William Martin, 1921-1929
  - Gyllenbogel, Karl Volter Boris, 1920-1921
  - Habsburg-Lorraine, Felix von, 1953
  - Habsburg-Lorraine, Otto von, 1946-1947
  - Habsburg-Lorraine, Robert von, 1953-1954
  - Habsburg-Lorraine, Rudolf von, 1953-1954
  - Hacker, William H. U., 1923
  - Hacking, Michael, 1954
  - Haines, Henry, 1935
  - Hale, George, undated
  - Hall, W. Reginald, Sir, Rear Adm., 1921-1932
  - Haller, General, 1920
  - Hallet, Max, 1919
  - Hallowell, John W., 1921
  - Halpern, Seymour, 1930
  - Halpert, Tadeusz, 1921-1953
  - Hamilton, William H., 1933
  - Hamlet, H. G., Capt., 1930
  - Hammond, Paul, 1921
  - Hammond, W. T. S., 1925-1931
  - Hanks, Stedman S., 1953
  - Hanna, Mathew E., 1928-1932
  - Hanna, Margaret M., 1932
  - Hanrahan, David C., 1922-1927
  - Hard, William, 1927-1936
  - Harding, Warren G., 1921
  - Harjes, H. H., Maj., 1918-1925
  - Harley, J. Eugene, 1926
  - Harman, Clifford B. (International League of Aviators, Paris), 1929
  - Harmon, Dudley, 1922
  - Harriman, Oliver B., 1923
  - Harris, Ray, 1930-1931
  - Harrison, Leland, 1919-1929
  - Harrison, Marguerite E., 1921
  - Harrison, Mrs., undated
  - Harts, William W., Gen., 1932
  - Haskell, Lewis W., 1924-1927
  - Hausmanowa, E., 1921
  - Haveman, Ir B. W., 1954
  - Havlicek, Frantisek S., 1931
  - Hawks, Stanley, 1924-1932
  - Hayden, H. B., 1929
  - Hayes, Ralph, 1919-1927
  - Haynes, John Randolph, 1920-1936
  - Healy, James A., 1920-1953 (Box 44)
  - Heath, Donald R., 1926
  - Hebb, Arthur, 1932
  - Heineman, Dannie N., 1930-1936
  - Helgert, Rudolph, 1926-1930
  - Hemphill, Alexander J., 1920
  - Henderson, Arthur, 1932
  - Henderson, James E., 1932
  - Hendrick, Anna, 1928
  - Hengstler, Herbert C., 1928-1935
  - Hennessy, Jean, 1926
  - Henry, I. I. R. (Mrs. Bayard), 1930-1936
  - Henry, Snowden, 1931
  - Henry Atterbury Smith, Inc., N.Y., 1929
  - Hensy, Margaret E., 1952-1954
  - Hepburn, Arthur J., Capt., 1927-1933
  - Herrick, Myron T., 1924-1929
  - Herse, Boguslaw, 1923
  - Hershfield, Isidor, 1922
  - Herter, Christian A., 1920-1927
  - Heymar, Alfred, 1919-1920
  - Hibbard, Frederick Pomeroy, 1922-1936
  - Hibben, John Grier, 1923
  - Hickerson, Jack D., 1933
  - High, Stanley, 1954
  - Hill, Edmund C., 1926
  - Hill, Hayward Gibbes, 1935-1953
  - Hill, Wallace, 1925
  - Hills, John W., 1933
  - Hills, Laurence (New York Herald), 1929-1932
  - Hilton, Charles E., Capt., 1934
  - Hinckle, Eugene, 1936
  - Hitch, Calvin M., 1924-1927
  - Hittell, Theodore H., 1902
  - Hoard, H. L., 1927
  - Hochart, W. H., 1932
  - Hodgson, Roberta, 1930
  - Hodson, Edward J.
    - 1922-1928
    - 1929-1936
  - Hodson, Francis, 1919-1921 (Box 45)
  - Hoehling, A. A., 1954
  - Holler, John E., 1923
  - Hollyday, T. Worthington, 1921
  - Holman, William J., 1954
  - Holquin y Caro, Uvaro, 1933-1934
  - Holt, George C., 1929
  - Holt, Winifred, 1920
  - Holvoet, Baron, 1929-1931
  - Honnold, William L., 1929-1934
  - Hooker, Katharine P., 1922-1933
  - Hooper, Jessie J. (Mrs. Ben), 1932
  - Hoover, Allan, 1932
  - Hoover, Herbert [See also: Miller, Bernice; SUBJECT FILE, Pecher, Charles and Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson; DIPLOMATIC POSTS, Poland, Relief Work, Correspondence]
    - Undated
    - 1915-1941
    - 1942-1954
    - Humorous correspondence on the subject of shingles, 1954
  - Hoover, Herbert, Jr., 1953-1954
  - Hoover, Lou Henry, 1918-1935
  - Hoover Overseas and War Service Organizations, N.Y., 1929-1930
  - Hoover War Library, Stanford, California, 1924
  - Hopkinson, Leslie W., undated
  - Horodyski, Jan, Count, 1920-1929
  - Hotel du Sport, Sannenmoser, Switzerland (Mr. Wehren), 1925
  - Hough, David L., 1929
  - Houghton, Alanson B., 1922-1926
  - Houghton(?), D., undated
  - Houghton, William H., 1929
  - Houghton Mifflin Company, Boston, 1930-1931
  - House, Edward M., Col., 1919-1933 (Box 46)
  - Hoving, Pauline, 1954
  - Howard, Finley K., 1935
  - Howard, Isabella, 1926
  - Howard, James H., 1930-1931
  - Howard, John K., 1935
  - Howe, F. C., 1930
  - Howell, W. S., Jr., 1921
  - Howie, John MacFarlane, 1930
  - Hubbard, Ella P., undated
  - Hubbard, G. Evans, 1928
  - Hubbard, Margaret, 1926
  - Hubscher, Carl P., 1925
  - Huddle, A. W., 1921
  - Hudson, Manley O., 1922-1924
  - Hughes, 1954
  - Hughes, Charles E., 1924-1942
  - Hughes, John C., 1953
  - Hukill, George R., 1926
  - Hull, Cordell, 1934-1942
  - Hull, William Ed (Republican National Committee, Chicago), 1932
  - Hunt, Edward Eyre, 1933
  - Hunt, Frazier, 1929
  - Hunt, Mary H., undated
  - Hunt, Sumner, Mrs., 1922
  - Hunt, William H., 1927
  - Hunter, Rosamond (Mrs. John R.), 1927
  - Huntington, Constant [See: Houghton Mifflin Company, Boston]
  - Huntington, Douglas St. George, 1921-1932
  - Hurley, William L., 1919-1924
  - Huston, Howard, 1926-1934
  - Hutchinson, C. K., 1933
  - Hutchinson, Lincoln, 1920-1929
  - Hutterly, William U., 1921
  - Hyde, James Hazen, 1921-1933
  - Hymans, Paul, 1930-1937
  - Hynderick de Theulegoet, Yves, Chevalier, and Claire, 1922-1953
  - Hynderick de Theulegoet, Ghislaine, 1952-1954
  - Irwin, Will, 1918-1922
  - Isaacs, C. Grant, 1941
  - Ischer, K., 1924
  - Iselin, Mrs., 1924
  - Iwanowski, Maj., 1921
  - Jack, James, Gen., 1954
  - Jackson, J. A., 1920
  - Jackson, John B., 1920
  - Jackson, Robert A., 1920-1921
  - Jackson, Thomas J., 1927
  - Jacobs, A. J., 1932
  - Jaqua, Ernest J. (Scripps College, California), 1933
  - Jacquet, 1927
  - Jacquetin-Joubert, J., Abbot, 1931
  - Jadwin, Edgar, 1921
  - James, A. L., Maj., 1918-1926
  - James, Henry, undated
  - James, Lucy (godmother of Michael Gibson, the former Mrs. Huntington Wilson)
    - 1920-1926
    - 1927-1930
    - 1931-1932 (Box 47)
    - 1933-1937
  - Janssen, Emmanuel, 1921
  - Jay, DeLancy K., 1920-1921
  - Jay, Peter Augustus [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson], 1918-1927
  - Jayne, R. K., 1927
  - Jeffes, W. F. H., 1924
  - Jefferson County Union, Fort Atkinson, Wisconsin, 1927
  - Jennings, Pauline, 1932
  - Joffre, Marshal Joseph Jacques Cesaire, 1918
  - John Burnham & Company, Chicago, 1920
  - Johnson, E. P., 1925
  - Johnson, H. H., 1921-1922
  - Johnson, Herschel V., 1927-1953
  - Johnson, Nelson Truslee, 1928-1936
  - Johnston, J. Kendall, 1929
  - Johnstone, Lady, 1923-1932
  - Johnstone, Edward, Mrs., undated
  - Joint Distribution Committee, N.Y., 1920
  - Jones, Hilary P., Adm., 1926-1936
  - Jones, Mary L., undated
  - Josephine-Charlotte, Princess of Belgium, 1948
  - Joyce, K. A., 1927
  - Joyce, Robert P., 1927
  - Joyce, W. E., 1921
  - Judge Company, N.Y., 1902
  - Jusserand, Jean Jules, 1917-1932
  - Kahn, Otto, 1923
  - Kauffman, Reginald Wright, 1930-1954
  - Keena, Leo John, 1921-1932
  - Keene, Peter J. T., 1929
  - Kelley, Robert Francis, 1934
  - Kellogg, Frank B., 1924-1934 (Box 48)
  - Kellogg, Vernon and Charlotte, 1918-1928
  - Kelly, D. Victor, 1930
  - Kelly, Madeleine, 1953
  - Kemp, Arthur, 1952
  - Kemp, Edwin C., 1923-1924
  - Kennaday, Paul, 1918
  - Kennt, Fred I., 1934
  - Kenyon, William Crellin, 1925
  - Kerchove de Denterghem, Charlie, Count, 1934-1954
  - Kerchove de Denterghem, Maggie, Countess, 1953-1954
  - Kerckhoff, Anne W. (Mrs. H. H.), 1931-1954
  - Kerckhoff, Louise E. (Mrs. W. G.), 1929-1936
  - Kerckhoff, Stephens, 1918
  - Kerckhoff, William G., 1924-1931
  - Kerney, James, 1919-1927
  - Kerr, Philip(?), 1930
  - Kerssenbrock, Therese S., Countess, 1952-1954
  - Key, David, 1932
  - Kiley, Henry Pat, 1930-1953
  - Kimens, Richard E., 1922
  - King, Alice (later, Mrs. Robert Forrest Stephen), 1919-1952
  - King, David, 1927
  - King, Lenora H., 1929
  - Kinsky, Alphy, Count, 1953 (Box 49)
  - Kinsky, Paula, Countess, 1921-1932
  - Kinsky, Frantisek, Count, 1931-1953
  - Kirby, John (Polish Government Loan National Campaign Committee, Washington, D.C.), 1920
  - Kirk, Alexander C., 1929-1933
  - Kirk, Alexandre, 1919
  - Kite, S., 1918
  - Kittredge, Tracy B., 1920-1930
  - Kleiderer, E. C., 1953
  - Klein, Julius, 1927-1953
  - Kleindienst, R. A., 1919-1920
  - Kleist, Baroness, 1930
  - Kleyn van Halluck, Fanny H., 1954
  - Klopstock, Paul, 1925
  - Klotz, Justine, 1921-1927
  - Knapp, H. S., 1919
  - Knight, Charly, 1918
  - Knoles, Tully C., 1929
  - Knox, Charles F., Jr., 1924
  - Koch, Gerald, 1930
  - Koch, Priscilla, 1926-1929
  - Koch de Gooreind, Manuela, 1928
  - Koch de Gooreind, Peter, 1932-1952
  - Koehler, Hugo W. [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Germany, General], 1919-1923
  - Kohlberg, Alfred, 1951-1953
  - Kohler, Louis, 1927
  - Kokot, S. N., 1921
  - Kolp, Victor, 1934
  - Komatsu, Takashi, 1935
  - Kotnowski, Leopold, 1924-1926
  - Krasitiski, Edouard, 1923
  - Kreisler, Fritz, 1938
  - Krock, Arthur, 1943
  - Kroll, Jacques, 1922
  - Krommer, Arnoldo, 1930
  - Krueger, J. W., Maj., 1922
  - Kuhn, Irene Corbally, 1951
  - Kunz, George F., 1920
  - Kwapiszewski, Michael, 1923-1936
  - Kyle, Pearl, 1932
  - Lada-Zablocki, K., 1921
  - Ladeuze, Monseigneur, 1928
  - Laemmle, Carl, 1937
  - La Follette, Suzanne, 1951
  - La Grandiere, Georges, Viscount, and Viscountess Monique de, 1952-1953
  - Lambert, Hansi, Baroness, 1953-1954
  - Lambert, Henri, 1927-1930
  - Lambert, Lucie, 1953
  - Lanctot, John B., 1952
  - Lane, Arthur Bliss [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Rogers Bill, Correspondence of Gibson]
    - 1919-1920
    - 1921-1922
    - 1923-1927 (Box 50)
    - 1928-1953
  - Lane, James Warren, 1920-1926
  - Lang, John P., 1929
  - Langelaan, G., 1927
  - Langhorne, Marshall, 1920
  - Lansing, Robert, 1918-1920
  - Lantsheere, Theo de, Viscount, 1924-1933
  - Larache, Count of Paris, 1942
  - Larner, Caroline S., 1910-1931
  - Lasocki, George, 1953-1954
  - Lathrop, Charles N., 1920
  - Laughlin, Irwin, 1919-1935
  - Lawford, Vincent, 1929
  - Lawrence, David, 1954
  - Lawrence, George W., 1933
  - Lawton, Elizabeth, 1927
  - Lay, Anne Howard (Mrs. Julius G.), 1934
  - Lay, Julius G., 1925-1935
  - Leach, Charles N., 1919-1920
  - The League of Nations Non-Partisan Association, N.Y. (Mrs. Waggoner), 1930
  - LeClerq, Frederick D. K., 1920
  - Ledebur, Eugene, Count [See also: SUBJECT FILE, Czechoslovakia], 1924-1935
  - Leech, Stephen, 1919
  - Le Gallais, Hughes, 1953
  - Leiser, Clara M., 1932
  - Leith-Ross, F. W., 1931
  - Leland, J. D., Mrs., 1930
  - Leonard, Bernard W., 1953
  - Leopold III, King of Belgium, 1930-1951
  - Lepage, George A., 1929-1930
  - Lepine, Jean, 1930
  - Lerchenfeld, Hugo, Count, and Countess Sophie von, 1926-1934
  - Le Tallec, Paul, 1924
  - Letcher, Marion, 1926-1933
  - Leval, Gaston de, 1915-1932
  - Lew, Isadore, 1924
  - Lewis, Mr. (Committee on Public Information, Paris), 1918
  - Lewis, James Hamilton, 1926
  - Librach, Jan, 1953
  - Librairie Hachette & Cie, Paris (Breton, G.), 1918
  - Ligne, Albert de, Prince, 1927-1953
  - Ligne, Charles de, Prince, undated
  - Ligne, Eugene de, Prince, 1928
  - Lima, Jose C. de, 1933
  - Lima de Silva, 1933
  - Lindbergh, Charles, 1933 (Box 51)
  - Lindley, Francis H., 1929
  - Lindsley, Henry, 1926
  - Lineberger, Walter Franklin, 1927
  - Linn, Howard and Lucy, 1926
  - Lipkowski, Stanislaw, 1924
  - Lippens, Maurice, 1929-1938
  - Lippmann, Walter, 1919-1931
  - Lissner, Meyer, 1920-1930
  - Lister, Winifred Harriett, 1928-1931
  - Lithuanian National Council, N.Y., 1920
  - Little, Anna (Mrs. John), 1928
  - Little, Charles G., 1924
  - Littlefield, Leland and Marian, 1919-1920
  - Lobkowicz, Anita (Mrs. Edward), 1952
  - Logan, F. A., 1932
  - Logan, James A., Jr., 1919-1929
  - Lokaly(?), F., 1927
  - Londonderry, Circe of, The Dowager Marquise, 1952
  - Long, Andrew T., Adm., 1927-1930
  - Long, Boaz W., 1920-1930
  - Long, Breckinridge, 1919-1920
  - Lonsdale, Jane White, 1920
  - Loomis, Julia S. (Mrs. Henry P.), American Society for Relief of Russian Exiles, Inc., N.Y., 1929-1932
  - Loraine, Percy, 1941
  - Lord, Robert H., 1919-1922
  - Los Angeles Chamber of Commerce (Arnoll, Arthur G.), 1928-1929
  - Loschitz, Valerie, 1931-1932
  - Lothian, Marquise Tony de, 1952-1954